

 \times

peterhoxuandung@outlook.com

+84 943 417821

Q

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

in

linkedin.com/in/peterhoxuandun g

8

+84943417821

()

github.com/PeterHo249

SKILLS

Flutter

Swift 4

Firebase

JavaScript

NodeJS

HTML

CSS

MongoDB

INTERESTS

Reading books

Listening to music

Traveling

Dung Xuan Ho

Mobile Developer

Highly responsibility, willingness to learn new things, independent working and positive teamwork attitudes. With the knowledge and skills which I learnt in university and the experience of Flutter, Swift, I want to become part of your mobile development team to create products together.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Software Engineering HCMVNU - University of Science

09/2015 – 05/2019 GPA: 7.96

EXPERIENCE

Fast Store - Freelance project (04/2019 – 05/2019)

- Built front-end for department store.
- Using Firebase to push notification.
- Tech stack: Flutter, Firebase Cloud Function and Cloud Messaging.

Success Hunter - Thesis project (09/2018 – 04/2019)

- Developed an application to support self development process using Gamification method.
- Tech stack: Flutter, Firebase service (Firestore, Cloud Function, Cloud Messaging, Cloud Pub/sub).
- Apple App Store: itunes.apple.com/us/app/success-hunter/id1451431732?mt=8.
- Google Play Store: play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.hoxuandung.successhunter.

Kanbanize - Course project (04/2018 – 07/2018)

- Developed an application to manage todo list with Kanban method on iOS.
- Language: Swift 4.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/KANBANize.

Rex Shop - Course project (04/2018 – 07/2018)

- Built a cameras and accessories shop website.
- Tech stack: Expressjs with HandlebarsJS, MongoDB.
- □ Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/rexshop.

Yame Shop - Course Project (04/2018 - 07/2018)

- Developed a clothes shop website with pure NodeJS and xml file.
- Tech stack: NodeJS, xml data file.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/yameshop.